export let listOfQuestions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "What is capital of Finland?",
    answer: "helsinki",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "What is capital of Germany?",
    answer: "berlin",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "What is capital of France?",
    answer: "paris",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "What is capital of Spain?",
    answer: "madrid",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "What is capital of Portugal?",
    answer: "lisbon",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "What is capital of Hungary?",
    answer: "budapest",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "What is capital of Italy?",
    answer: "rome",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "What is capital of Norway?",
    answer: "oslo",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "What is capital of Croatia?",
    answer: "zagreb",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "What is capital of Sweden?",
    answer: "stockholm",
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: "What is capital of Malta?",
    answer: "valletta",
  },
];
